SB

Scott Braaten

FRONT END DEVELOPER

- (703) 638-2631
- sbraaten95@gmail.com
- North Palm Beach, FL
- linkedin.com/in/sbraaten95
- Skype: Scott Braaten
- % scottbraaten.com

ABOUT ME

Highly analytical problem solver with an interest in new technologies and a love for JavaScript. Known to be a self-starter and a leader.

Greatly values teamwork.

4+ years of experience with objectoriented programming, particularly with JavaScript. Additional interests include data science, biology, psychology, and philosophy. Among the top students in Palm Beach Atlantic's Computer Science Department, commended for being detail oriented and learning rapidly.

SKILLS

Languages:

JavaScript, HTML, CSS, SQL, Python, C#, Ruby, Java, Visual Basic, PHP

Frameworks:

React, Angular, Node.js, Bootstrap, Rails, Android, .NET, Django, SASS

Database Management: MongoDB, MySQL, SQL Server, SQLite

EDUCATION

Computer Science, B.S (3.66 GPA)

Palm Beach Atlantic University

2019 – 2021 (Current)

Psychology Studies (3.50 GPA)

Northern Virginia Community College 2018 - 2019

Computer Science Studies (3.20 GPA) San Diego Mesa College 2015 - 2016

EXPERIENCE

Customer Service Representative

Ethos Data Management / West Palm Beach, FL / June 2019 – August 2019

Assisted customers with SEO on their websites and Google Business Listings.

Teaching Assistant

Coding Dojo / McLean, VA / August 2016 – January 2017

Completed Coding Dojo's full stack development bootcamp and assisted other students learning how to create websites using:

- MEAN stack
- Django
- Ruby on Rails

PROJECTS

FitnessApp

A Fitness app for counting calories and protein. Utilizes the Nutritionix API for food data. Programmed using the Django Stack (Python, MySQL).

LiveLive

A website facilitating live YouTube video watching parties, made with the MEAN stack. Utilizes angular directives to build video sessions dynamically.

Portfolio

My portfolio website showcasing my different projects, built with react, react bootstrap, and react router. Deployed on Firebase.